require_relative 'challenges.rb'

# title: "",
#MIND category

smart_ass = Challenge.new(title: "Smart Ass", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: " Pontificate on a topic chosen by the opposing team for 60 seconds without any fillers (er, um, uh, y’know) or pauses over 3 seconds.", solution: nil)
phone_number = Challenge.new(title: "Phone Number", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: "Have an opposing team write down a 10-digit number on a piece of paper and hand it to a player on your team. The player can then speak the number only once. The remaining players on the team then have to keep the number in their heads (no speaking) for 30 seconds starting after the last number was spoken. During the 30 seconds the opposing team can use whatever verbal attacks they want in order to confuse the other players.", solution: nil)
newlywed_game = Challenge.new(title: "The NewlyWed Game", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: "Write down your favorite _______ on a sheet of paper while simultaneously having a teammate write down YOUR favorite _______ on another.", solution: "Flip the papers at the same time to show everyone. You win this card if it’s the same you and your teammate had the same answer.")
im_going_to_paddys_pub = Challenge.new(title: "Im Going to Paddys Pub", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: "One person from team plays this game. The one who draws this card starts by saying, “I’m going to Paddy’s Pub and I need to get a ______.” After that, the ensuing player repeats the drink the previous player said, but adds another drink to the list. Keep going until Players mess up, single elimination style. Last two players flip a coin to determine who takes a shot or drinks a glass of wine. All other losers drink as per the usual.", solution: nil)
spelling_bee = Challenge.new(title: "Spelling Bee", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: " One player from each team attempts to spell words from the rule book without pausing as soon as a neutral party who reads the words from the rulebook out loud. Single elimination, standard spelling bee rules.", solution: nil)
three_cups_and_a_coin = Challenge.new(title: "Three Cups and a Coin", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: " An opposing team takes three Solo cups and places a coin underneath one of them. The person who drew this card must select the correct cup. The player may watch as the person switches everything around. The opposing team(s) have the chance to steal, however, they cannot earn the card simply by faking-out the team which drew this card. This card must be earned in its own right.", solution: nil)
spatula = Challenge.new(title: "Spatula", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: "All play: Hand me the spatula.", solution: "?")
speech = Challenge.new(title: "Speech", level: 1, category: "MIND", prompt: "You have three minutes to give a speech on any topic you wish for 90 to 120 seconds. You must use three words/phrases that the opposing team gives you during the speech in order to win this card. You have 30 seconds to prepare.", solution: nil)

#TRIVIA Category

film_plot = Challenge.new(title: "Film Plot", level: 1, category: "TRIVIA", prompt: "Give a synopsis of the plot of three separate films in under 15 seconds.", solution: nil)
the_dennis_system = Challenge.new(title: "The Dennis System", level: 1, category: "TRIVIA", prompt: "Name the six steps of the dennis system:", solution: "(Demonstrate value, Engage physically, Nurture dependence, Neglect emotionally, Inspire hope, Separate entirely)")
dennis_is_asshole = Challenge.new(title: "Dennis Is Asshole", level: 1, category: "TRIVIA", prompt: "Dennis is asshole. Why charlie hate?", solution: "Because Dennis is a bastard man.")
common_core = Challenge.new(title: "Common Core", level: 1, category: "TRIVIA", prompt: "Have your opponents give you two two-digit numbers to multiply in your head. You have 30 seconds. Opponents may verbally harass you during this challenge.", solution: nil )
mac_system = Challenge.new(title: "Mac System", level: 1, category: "TRIVIA", prompt: "Name the three steps of the Mac system.", solution: "Move in After Completion")
original_mf = Challenge.new(title: "The Original Motherfucker", level: 1, category: "TRIVIA", prompt: "Who was the original motherfucker?", solution: "Oedipus")

#Artistry

sensual_drawing = Challenge.new(title: "Sensual Drawing", level: 1, category: "Artistry", prompt: "Draw an image to the best of your abilities on a teammate’s back. First team to identify the drawing strictly by feel, wins the card. You must tell the opposing team(s) what the image is going to be before you begin.", solution: nil)
illustrator_theatre = Challenge.new(title: "Illustrators Theatre", level: 1, category: "Artistry", prompt: "All play: The person that draws this card must come up with something for everyone to draw. A teammate must charade out the clue while all other players attempt to draw it. No talking is allowed, no gesturing is allowed by the drawing teammate. There are 45 seconds on the clock, after which the teams present their drawing and see if they were correctly able to interpret their teammates’ charade. In the event that multiple teams get it, the winner is decided with a coin flip.")
perfect_geometry = Challenge.new(title: "Perfect Geometry", level: 1, category: "Artistry", prompt: "One person from each team draws a freehand circle. Get a piece of paper and draw a symbol in place of your name in the corner and draw a perfect circle in the middle. Circles are then voted on in single elimination. (Be objective). In the event of a tie, coin-flip.")
sketch_artist = Challenge.new(title: "Sketch Artist", level: 1, category: "Artistry", prompt: "Player who selects this card has 1 minute to draw any other player in the room, as a rapist, a pedophile, or a murderer. Player’s own team has two chances to (A) guess the person drawn in the picture and (B) guess what he/she is. If correctly guessed, subject must drink a full serving of whatever they have. If not, everyone else must drink a full serving of whatever they have because there’s a sex  offender/killer on the loose and its all your fault. Chance to steal.")
feet = Challenge.new(title: "Feet", level: 1, category: "Artistry", prompt: "One member from each team draws a picture of a sexual position with their foot using a marker. First team to guess within 2 guesses wins. Write down what you will draw on a sheet of paper and keep it to yourself until all guesses have been made to prevent cheating.")

#Puzzles

jigsaw = Challenge.new(title: "Jigsaw", level: 1, category: "Puzzles", prompt: "Complete a puzzle in under five minutes. Every member of the team must finish at least one glass of wine.")
memory = Challenge.new(title: "Memory", level: 1, category: "Puzzles", prompt: "One player from each team will take all cards out of a deck. Mix them up and arrange them on a table face down. Participants will have 30 seconds to prepare. A game of Memory will commence: Spades match with Clubs and Hearts match with Diamonds (e.g. black-to-black and red-to-red). Those playing Memory are the only ones who can look at the cards, everyone else must stay back but can verbally harass the players to distract them. Once a player misses twice after his/her first match, then he/she is out.")
inception = Challenge.new(title: "Inception", level: 1, category: "Puzzles", prompt: "You have 2 minutes to draw a maze that a member of an opposing team has to solve. Maze must have a solvable route or drawing team must finish their beverages. If the opposing person solves the maze in 1 minute, they get the card. If not, he/she must finish his/her beverage and the team that drew the maze gets to keep the card. Card cannot be earned by maze-drawing team if maze is not solvable.")
paper_planes = Challenge.new(title: "Paper Planes", level: 1, category: "Puzzles", prompt: "All Play: Everyone makes a paper airplane. Team with the farthest plane wins this card.")
honorable_mention = Challenge.new(title: "Honorable Mention", level: 1, category: "Puzzles", prompt: "Opposing team chooses a movie. Another team chooses a player to act out the movie using only their hands and sound effects. No actual words may be spoken and actor must remain seated. If team guesses correctly within 30 seconds, they get the card.")
jenga_irl = Challenge.new(title: "Jenga IRL", level: 1, category: "Puzzles", prompt: "All play: See who can stack any objects in the room the highest in thirty seconds. The team with the tallest tower or the last team to knock over its own tower wins. DESTROYING ANY GAME SUPPLIES MEANS YOU MUST FINISH YOUR DRINK")
